TUC Periodicals and Serials on Microfilm 6112 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
TUC Periodicals and Serials on Microfilm
1918-1977
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Trades Union Congress (TUC)
6112 mf
1.89 cubic feet
17 microfilm reels
Records, microfilm.
5800424
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 23, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 23, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The Trades Union Congress (TUC) is a national trade union centre, a federation of trade unions in England and Wales, representing the majority of trade unions. There are fifty-eight affiliated unions with a total of about 6.2 million members, around half of whom are represented by Unite or UNISON.
The TUC's decision-making body is the Annual Congress, which takes place in September. Between congresses decisions are made by the General Council, which meets every two months. An Executive Committee is elected by the Council from its members. [wikipedia]
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6113 mf: TUC General Committee Minutes and Papers on Microfilm 6114 mf: TUC Archives on The Mining Crisis and The Genral Strike on Microfilm 6115 fiche: TUC Archives on Microfiche
Collective bargaining-- Great Britain; Labor unions-- Great Britain; Industrial relations-- Great Britain; Trades Union Congress. --Archives
5800424
- The British Worker 1926, 1927, Industrial News-1926-1931 (Reel 1)
- Industrial News 1932-1938 (Reel 2)
- Industrial News 1939-1941, 1946-1957 (Reel 3)
- Industrial News 1958-1975 (Reel 4)
- Monthly News Letter 1935-1937 then Industrial News, Letter for Women 1937-1962, TUC Industrial Relations Bull. 1972-1975 (Reel 5)
- The Industrial Review 1927-1933, International Trades Union Review 1918-1922 (Reel 6)
- British Trades Union Review, Aug. 1919-Jul. 1921, then The Labour Magazine, May 1922-Apr. 1925. (Reel 7)
- The Labour Magazine, May 1925-Apr. 1929 (Reel 8)
- The Labour Magazine, May 1929-Apr. 1933 (Reel 9)
- The Labour Magazine, May 1933-Aug. 1933 then Labour, Sep. 1933-Aug. 1936. Copy 2. (Reel 10)
- The Labour Magazine, May 1933-Aug. 1933 then Labour, Sep. 1933-Aug. 1936 [duplicate of reel 10] (Reel 11)
- Labour, Sep. 1936-Aug. 1940 (Reel 12)
- Labour, Sep. 1940-1947 (Reel 13)
- Labour, Sep. 1947-1954 (Reel 14)
- Labour, Jan. 1955-Dec. 1963 (Reel 15)
- Labour, Mar. 1965-Sep. 1977 (Reel 16)
- Review of Collective Bargaining Developments 1970-1973, Trade Union Defense Bull. 1927 (Reel 17)